www.DHIYAFARIS.com
Nica?
Nica. There's somebody at the door
I'm busy.
Nica, please.
God!
What are you doing
that's so important?
I was playing solitaire.
The computer cheats, you know
Yeah, well, I'm used to that.
Morning
Hi.
Got a delivery for
Mrs. Sarah Pierce?
I'll... I'll sign for it
Cool.
You know, you don't
look like a Mrs.
Oh I'm...
I'm not.
It's for my mother.
Oh, God. I'm back living
with my mother, too.
It's just a fucking
nightmare, right?
You have no idea.
Wait a minute. Oh, my God.
I know you
You do?
Yeah, yeah. It was City College.
The Psych Department, right?
That was me.
Well, when'd you graduate?
I didn't. I never completed my thesis.
On what?
Completion anxiety.
Thought only guys got that.
So, is your mom
home now or what?
Yeah.
Too bad.
Well,... see you around.
Bye.
Was that guy hitting on me?
Baby, you're beautiful.
Thank you. But I think that
guy was hitting on me.
Maybe I should go ask him out
Nica.
He was just being nice.
I'm sorry.
Honey, I just don't ever
want to see you get hurt.
I thought you swore off the
Home Shopping Network.
I haven't bought
anything in three weeks.
Maybe you have a secret admirer.
- You sound threatened.
- No. Not at all.
I just wouldn't want
to see you get hurt.
Who's it from?
It doesn't say.
Must be some kind of joke.
I don't get it
Neither do I.
He's cute.
If you say so.
Hi. I'm Chucky.
Wanna play?
Alice will love him.
I DVR'd Real Housewives.
I'm going to make tuna melts later.
Okay?
Mom?
Oh, God.
Mom! My mom.
I need an ambulance right away.
It's my mother.
I don't know. I don't know.
There's so much blood.
Nica.
I'm sorry.
She was fine.
She was taking her meds,
she was painting again.
No, She was fine
No.
How could she do that, Barbie?
How could she do
that to herself?
You... you remember Father Frank.
Ah... yes.
Hello, Father.
I'm so very sorry for
your loss, Nica.
Thank you.
Your sister just thought it might
be a good idea for me to come.
I appreciate it.
But you know my mother and I both
left the church a long time ago.
But not in the eyes of God.
I just thought it might be nice for
us to have someone to talk to.
We have each other.
Nica.
We have to pray for her.
To be forgiven.
She was sick.
You can't judge her.
No one is judging her.
In fact, the church's official
response to a situation like this
is not to judge, but to pity.
My mother and I have had quite
enough pity, thank you.
I understand.
It was my fault.
I should have seen it coming.
Nica, you cannot blame yourself.
She was supposed to be
taking care of you.
Hey
Hey, Ian.
Gimme a hug.
Is that a new chair?
Yeah.
It's cool
Thank you.
This... this is Jill,
my new au pair.
No, I'm just the nanny.
Hi.
I'm so sorry, Nica.
Thank you.
I'm... I'm glad you're here.
Come here, you.
I'm so happy to see you.
Me, too.
Did Grandma go to heaven?
Yes, sweetie, she did.
Hey, I have a surprise for you.
That's funny.
Mommy, I have to go to the bathroom
Okay. Jill will take you.
You show her the way.
Mommy needs to talk to Aunty Nica.
Jill, let's go.
I think I'm going to go with them.
Okay?
Remember, you don't
have to lock the door.
But somebody might come in
We won't let anybody in.
But what about you guys?
Honey, we really don't want
to see you do your business.
Okay, bye.
So listen, how much is
she paying you again?
$400 a week.
That's more than I make.
Well, maybe you should
consider a career change.
Hey, I'd be a great nanny.
$400 a week!
Man
Yeah, but no benefits.
What's your name?
Alice? Alice, open
the door, honey!
the door right now.
He scared me half to death.
What is this?
Well, Mom left the
house to both of us.
So?
So.
I think we should consider selling.
What are you talking about?
Nica, this place is fabulous.
It's so much closer to us,
we'd get to see you way more often.
And with your half of what
we could get for the house,
you'd be set for the
rest of your life.
This isn't about me.
This is about money.
Well, you know we've
been struggling.
Print media is dead.
Ian's working at Starbucks.
We're going to have to send
Alice to public school.
And she so had her heart set on
St. Bridget's.
I don't want to deprive
my child.
You have a live-in nanny.
Well, actually, that's
not really working out.
Barb,
this is my home.
Nica, I know this is hard.
But do you really think you can
manage here all by yourself?
Mom would have wanted you
to be taken care of.
That's all she ever wanted.
We're back.
You found him
He was in the bathroom.
Really?
You know, I think Grandma would have
wanted you to take care of him.
It was obviously sent here by mistake.
It must belong to someone else.
And Alice, you already have
too many dolls as it is.
Yeah, but Chucky's my
friend till the end!
I actually think it's a really nice gesture.
Thank you, Aunty Nica.
It's a doll.
What's the worst that
can happen, huh?
I like to be hugged.
I like to hug you, too, Chucky.
What's that, Chucky?
Chucky wants to know
what's for dinner.
I guess I better get started
in the kitchen.
Don't be silly.
You guys are my guests and you must
be exhausted from your flight,
please, just make
yourselves at home.
Father Frank, you will stay
for dinner, won't you?
Well, I... I'd love to, Nica.
Thanks.
You're going to make dinner.
For six.
Seven.
Well,
I will need a chef's assistant.
And Chucky can be my assistant.
Great.
Let's get cooking.
It's really good
It's the oregano.
Did you finish setting the table?
Almost.
Pay the toll
We're on a roll.
No, honey, don't touch that.
Can you grab me the napkins?
The fancy ones from
last Christmas.
This smells delicious.
Thanks
Come on, Chucky.
Wow. Look at this, Nica. You've
really outdone yourself this time.
We are going to sit right here.
Barb, sit next to me here
Okay. If you insist.
Wow. Look at this
Thanks, Jill. Make yourself comfortable.
Oh, you brought out the nice china.
Father, would you
like to say grace?
Bless us, oh Lord,
and these Thy gifts
which we are about to
receive from Thy bounty.
Stop
Through Jesus Christ our Lord we pray.
Amen.
Jill?
Thank you, Ian.
Don't mind if I do
How about you, Father?
Oh no. I'm good.
I am starving.
Wait.
Your daddy would like
to make a toast.
To the chef.
Thank you.
I had a great assistant.
I love chili
Do you really?
Yeah
Me, too. Love it.
Is there meat in this?
No. Not at all.
It's vegetarian.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God
What?
This is amazing!
I know. I can't believe
there's no meat in this.
It's so hearty.
It's the oregano.
This is just the way my
mama used to make it.
Nica, could you pass me
the salt?
Thank you.
You know, that doll,
it looks really familiar somehow.
Father, come on.
Good Guy dolls were all
the rage back in the 80s.
My brother even had one
So did mine.
Are you serious?
Yes.
Oh, come on.
I seem to remember
seeing them on the news?
I remember seeing people
standing in line overnight
just to get their hands
on one of these.
They were right up there with
Smurfs and Cabbage Patch Kids.
Alice, honey, is something wrong?
It tastes funny.
Maybe we put too
much oregano in.
Alice, sweetheart,
it's not that bad.
Eat it.
Father, are you all right?
I'm... I'm so sorry,
I'm going to have to be going.
Oh, my God, Father, are you ill?
Oh, no, I'm fine.
I... I have an appointment
back at the church.
Nica, thank you so much,
the chili was delicious.
Father, are you?
No, please forgive me.
I don't mean to be rude.
I'll see you all in the
morning at the cemetery.
Good night.
I'm so sorry.
Where is he?
This way.
What happened?
Lost control, hit them head on.
Probably drunk.
No, no, this isn't right.
I know him, I'm in his parish.
He doesn't drink anymore
You sure about that?
He's my sponsor.
Stanton, you're going to need
a drink after you see this.
Jesus Christ.
Steel's got him pinned.
He's lost a shitload of blood,
but we just can't
tell from where.
Father, can you hear me?
Father?
Just hang on! We're
going to get you out.
What the hell are you waiting for?
Get this shit off him!
I can't make that call
He's bleeding to death! Get him out!
Okay, set in
On my count.
One, two, pull.
This is an oldie.
Oh, my God. Is that you?
Shut up
You're so cute.
It's called baby fat.
Look, I didn't say anything.
Go back to sleep
Will do.
Look at her.
She's so happy.
What happened to your dad?
He drowned that year,
couple of weeks
before Nica was born.
Mom was never the same
after that.
Who's that?
Some neighbor back
in Chicago, I guess.
What a weirdo.
Hey there, missy, what'cha up to?
Chucky's gone.
Not again
Well, where did you leave him?
I didn't.
He's hiding.
Okay, time for bed.
And don't forget to brush
your teeth and your hair.
What about Chucky?
Jill will go look for Chucky.
I'll give you a hand, Jill
We're not done here yet.
I think he's hiding under my bed
Don't worry, we'll find him.
I'm going to be right back.
Are you sure you didn't
leave him downstairs?
I didn't leave him anywhere.
He's hiding.
There he goes!
I am not in the mood for this.
Need a hand?
I need a fucking search party!
I have looked over every inch of this
house and I can't find him anywhere.
God, I've missed you
Shut up.
You found him.
I think she wanted you
to find him.
You know, I haven't been
spending enough time with her.
It's like if I'm not working,
I'm just so tired all the time.
Life is short!
Did they always say that?
I don't know.
Listen, little man, what else are you,
telling my kid behind my back, huh?
I like to be hugged.
And?
Hey. Wanna play?
Is that it?
Hi. I'm Chucky.
And I'm your friend
'till the end.
That one's a classic.
And it works on so many
different levels.
Yeah, the 80s were awesome.
Did you find him yet?
Yeah, we found him!
I'll take him up.
Ian?
Anyone?
Hello?
Oh, shit.
Coming!
See, with her,
it's always something.
She needs my help and
then resents me for it.
You're the only one who
really appreciates me.
You know,
I was thinking.
We can get by without the money.
You don't have to sell.
I mean, this is her home.
She's a mess.
You can see that.
Oh, crap.
There you are, Chucky! We've
been looking for you everywhere.
Hey, want to play?
I didn't know you could do that.
Playtime's over.
It's time for bed.
Can you read us a bedtime story?
Aunty Nica's tired, sweetie.
We'll let her rest now.
I'm fine.
It's important that you
don't overextend yourself.
Don't you think I'm the best judge
of when I'm overextending myself?
Frankly, no
Really.
I don't think you realize
the strain you're under.
There's no shame in admitting
that you need help.
You mean "assistance."
Nica, I am worried about your heart.
Okay?
Dr. Masur said I was fine, Barb.
You're at significant risk of it
happening again, you know that.
13% of all T5 paraplegics...
I know the statistics.
Dr. Masur said that
extreme stress,
any kind of even mild
shock could bring it on.
And since last night, God knows
you've had plenty of both.
Alice, sweetheart,
please come down from there.
I'm disabled, Barb,
I am not a child.
And I'm perfectly capable
of taking care of myself.
Aunty Nica,
you're bleeding.
Oh, my God
I got it. Okay?
It almost looks like
a knife wound.
You must have cut
yourself making dinner.
I didn't
Doesn't it hurt?
No. No, don't worry, sweetie.
She can't feel a thing.
All right, come on. Come on.
Off to bed now.
Good night, Aunty Nica.
Good night, baby.
Sweet dreams.
Now I lay me down to sleep,
I pray the Lord my soul to keep.
If I shall die before I wake,
I pray the Lord my soul to take.
God bless Grandma, and Mommy,
and Daddy, and Jill.
And especially Aunty Nica.
What about Chucky?
He says there is no God.
Who said that?
Chucky did.
He said that life's a bitch and then
you die, bleeding like a stuck pig.
Alice. You know it's
not nice to curse.
I don't curse, Mommy.
Chucky did.
Mommy, am I going to die?
No. Of course not, sweetie.
Grandma died. And Chucky
says we're all going to die.
Alice, who really told you that?
Was it Jill?
No.
Was it your daddy?
No, it was Chucky.
Okay.
Can't we sleep in with you tonight?
Alice, we've talked about this.
You're a big girl now.
It's only a storm.
And Jill's going to
be in in a while.
Don't forget Chucky!
Don't worry, Chucky.
It's only a storm.
Ma'am, thank you for holding.
The package...
...evidence depository.
I'm sorry, you're breaking up.
Did you say "evidence depository"?
Hello, are you there?
Chucky, I'm scared.
You fucking should be.
Sorry.
We found him.
She sure loves that thing
Yeah. She sure does.
But you know, I just called
the delivery company,
and they said it was sent from
an evidence depository.
As in crime scene evidence?
I don't know. Maybe I heard them wrong.
The connection was bad.
I'm sure that's it.
Yeah, but we still don't know
who sent it.
I don't care if it was
the Manson Family.
Anything that keeps her
this happy is fine by me.
She's been so sad lately.
I better get to bed.
Long day tomorrow.
Good night
Good night, Jill.
Andy Barclay.
Charles.
She's up.
Women.
Can't live with 'em.
Period.
Shit.
What's going on?
Power's out again.
I'm going to go check on Alice.
What about Jill?
What about her?
Well, come on, Barb.
You're paying her $400 a week
to take care of our kid.
Don't you think she can handle it?
Ian, she's afraid of the dark.
It's storming out.
She might need me.
Who exactly, might need you?
Who do you think?
Right now I'm not sure
what to think.
You know...
Don't try to implicate me
in your sick fantasies, it's okay?
I've seen the way
you look at her.
Ditto.
Ian, I am not sleeping
with the nanny.
No, of course, you couldn't
be that stupid, Barb.
Knowing that if I could prove such a thing,
I could easily take Alice away from you.
Or I could just check
the footage.
What are you talking about?
The footage from the nanny cam.
What nanny cam?
The one I hid in the doll today.
You are not taking my daughter
away from me. Do you hear me?
I am not going to let
you destroy this family
because of your sick,
paranoid accusations.
Oh, that's right tune me out.
Let Barb take care of everything. That's
what you always do anyway, right?
You latte-making loser.
What's the word from Forensics?
Won't know anything for sure
till they cook his blood.
Hey, you talk to anyone at
St. Paul's yet?
Said he was out at the
Pierce house all day.
Okay, well, maybe they'll
have some answers for us.
I'm going to head out there now.
Alice?
Alice! I don't have time
to play games.
Barb?
Barb!
Barb, where's Alice?
Playing fucking hide and seek.
Barb, put him down.
What is wrong with you?
Look, I know that this
sounds nuts, but that doll,
I think that there's something in it
Wait a second. You know about this?
Well, I think that I do
You know what's in this?
Do you?
Why didn't you tell me?
I'm trying to tell you
Wait, wait. When did you find out?
What does it matter?
It matters to me.
It matters to me that my own
sister is out to get me.
No. No, no, no, you don't
understand, this...
I understand perfectly.
I understand you resent the fact
that I actually have a life.
No, Barb, this isn't about anything that..
Well, you know what, Nica?
It isn't my fault. Okay?
What happened to you
isn't my fault.
And it isn't my fault that
you dropped out of school,
and it isn't my fault that you chose
to never leave this goddamned house.
I mean, what the hell were you
waiting for, a sign from God?
No, Barb! Just put the
fucking doll down!
Fuck you, Nica.
Barb!
Alice! Get down here!
Jill?
Ian!
Shit!
Alice?
Alice, don't touch anything.
You hear me?
Alice, you are in big trouble,
young lady!
Alice!
Alice, please.
Mommy is just about sick to death
of all of you.
Alice?
Alice, you come out
here right this minute.
Oh, my God.
Alice.
Alice is mine.
Now she knows...
there is no God.
You have your mother's eyes.
And they were always too
fucking close together!
No!
Barbie?
Nica.
I'm gonna get you.
Alice!
Ian! Ian!
Ian!
What, what?
Ian, they're dead!
What are you talking about?
Barb, Jill, they're dead,
and I can't find Alice!
No! No! He's still out there!
Who?
Chucky!
Alice! Alice!
I gotta go find Alice.
Ian!
What?
Ian, if you see Chucky, whatever
you do, just leave him alone.
Chuck... What are
you talking about?
Just stay away from that doll!
Alice?
Ian?
Ian!
Alice?
No!
Nica!
Nica, what the hell
are you doing?
He did it! It was him!
Nica! Look at me!
Give me the ax.
What? No!
Now, give me the goddamn ax!
Oh, my God. Nica,
what have you done?
Ian. Ian, please.
You know I would never...
Oh, my God.
Ian. Ian. Take this.
I need you to inject it
under my rib.
Ian.
Ian. Ian, what are you doing?
What the hell have you done
with my daughter, Nica?
Ian, where's Chucky?
You're sick!
Ian, I swear to God,
I can prove it!
And so can I.
Hey, Barb, check this out.
RadioShack, 450 bucks.
Oh, and by the way, if you're watching
this, I put it on your MasterCard.
Where are you, Alice?
They'll never find
me in here, Chucky.
This is the best game
of hide and seek ever.
Just keep your
fucking mouth shut.
Chucky, stop cursing.
Say hi to the little woman
for me.
Maybe not.
Your turn.
My turn.
You're Charles Lee Ray.
My friends call me Chucky.
You're dead.
No, you are.
Why us?
Didn't your mother
ever mention me?
I'm an old friend of the family.
Charles, come over here.
I wanna introduce
you to someone.
October 27th.
Okay.
Right against my rib cage.
Soon enough. Cannot
come soon enough.
Charles, this is Sarah.
Hi
How do you do?
Her husband, Daniel
Hello, sir.
Hi, Daniel. Nice to meet you.
And this is Barb.
She has her mother's eyes.
Such a nice, happy family.
But not for long.
You like 'em?
Mmm-hmm.
They're beautiful, thank you.
Difficult to find right now.
They're not exactly in season.
Anyway, enjoy.
It's gettin' late, and I'm gonna
go pick up Barbie at day care.
No!
I mean, shouldn't we have
some time alone together?
What about family time?
Later.
Right now I want to
have you all to myself.
Sarah. Sarah,
you've had me all day.
It isn't enough.
That's a selfish fucking attitude
for a mother to take.
You don't wanna share me
with her?
No. No.
Well, what's gonna happen
when the baby comes?
Are you gonna keep her from me, too?
Because that would be very hurtful to me.
And you wouldn't wanna see me
get hurt, would you?
Would you?
No. No.
I don't wanna see you get hurt.
I don't wanna see anybody get hurt.
Okay.
I'm gonna go get Barbie.
No! Please, please!
Please don't.
Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
You told them about us?
There is no us.
Why?
Why would you want to
destroy this family?
You destroyed my family.
No.
I told you,
I've always had a thing
for families.
No!
Especially kids.
You did this to me?
No, Nica, you did this to me.
You and your mommy.
She betrayed me.
Got me killed.
But I knew a way to come back.
Give me the power.
I beg of you!
Took me 25 years,
but believe me,
it was worth the wait.
25 years.
Since then, a lot of
families have come and gone.
The Barclays,
the Kincaids, the Tillys,
but Nica, your family
was always my favorite.
And now,
you're the last one standing.
So to speak.
You know, you remind me
a lot of Andy Barclay.
He was a whiny little
bitch, just like you.
Did you kill him, too?
More or less.
I killed his childhood.
And the truth is,
I killed you 25 years ago.
Didn't I, Nica?
You haven't been living.
You can't call this living.
You've just been
on life support.
Time to pull the fucking plug.
So you never actually killed
Andy Barclay, did you?
What?
You know, it's called
completion anxiety.
It's very common in males.
You are a male, aren't you?
I'm gonna kill you slow.
Yeah, no, I get that.
25 years. Must be the
slowest murder in history.
I mean, what are you waiting for?
A sign from God?
No!
You feel that, don't ya?
You wanna play, motherfucker?
Let's play.
Police. Open up.
Help! Help me!
Based on the evidence, the defendant
is declared legally incompetent
and remanded indefinitely to a
facility for the criminally insane.
I'm alive, you son of a bitch.
You hear me?
I'm still alive!
Please leave a message.
Hey, it's me. I'm on my way.
And don't forget my money.
They never learn.
So who's next?
Next.
Good afternoon.
Three-day, two-day,
or overnight?
Overnight.
It's extremely urgent.
Fragile?
Surprisingly not.
Approximate value?
Well, my mother always used to say
you can't put a price on love.
Under 250, then.
Would you like to
insure the package?
Oh, that won't be necessary.
It protects you and
it protects the recipient.
I doubt that.
Perishable goods?
Live animal?
Just put "other."
Grandma, I'm home.
Grandma?
And how are you today?
Oh, I'm fine. I'm fine.
Feeling lucky?
Yeah.
Oh, that's great, Bunny.
As you know,
Bunny has won 17,000...
Chucky, you found me!
I told you I would.
Where's Grandma?
In the cellar.
What's she doing down there?
Nothin'.
Chucky, Mommy and Daddy
are dead.
Aunty Nica killed them.
But I'm your friend
till the end, Alice.
And now it's time to play.
Hide and seek?
Hide the soul.
And guess what?
You're it.
Why do I always have to be it?
Because you're somebody that
no one would ever suspect.
Now, close your eyes.
Give me the power, I beg of you.
Package for you
Really?
Maybe you won something.
Must be my lucky day.
Have a good one.
Thanks. You, too.
Oh, boy. A seat!
Get your seat off of my feet.
But what feet?
Hello? Oh, hi, Mom,
how you doing?
I'm sorry I didn't call.
I meant to.
Yeah, I'm definitely coming
for my birthday tomorrow.
No, don't get me anything.
Do me a favor, Ma,
no surprises, okay?
Yeah. I'll be there, like, noon?
1:00?
What are you making for dinner?
Yeah?
How's Mike doing?
Well, tell him I said hello.
Yeah.
All right
Come on, open up, open up!
Well, I'll see you
around that time.
Okay.
Play with this.
Andy...
www.DHIYAFARIS.com